[
  {
    "question": "What version of the game were you playing?",
    "answer": [
      "Diablo II: Lord of Destruction 1.14d",
      "PlugY 14.03"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Were you playing single player or multiplayer?",
    "answer": "Single player"
  },
  {
    "question": "Was this a softcore or hardcore character?",
    "answer": "Softcore"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long did it take to go from level 1 to level 99?",
    "answer": "It took 789 Hours over the span of 15 months which averages out to be about 1.75 hours per day. Note that this includes leveling a Smiter to obtain torches, farming keys, farming torches, and running Lower Kurast for runes."
  },
  {
    "question": "How long did it take to go from level 98 to level 99?",
    "answer": "It took 175 hours and about 5000 Chaos Sanctuary runs. Note that I saved my Ancients Quests to complete at level 98, so if you don't do that, it will take a little longer."
  },
  {
    "question": "Did you obtain all the holy grail items?",
    "answer": "No, there were 15 holy grail items I did not obtain."
  },
  {
    "question": "Did you obtain every rune?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this the first time you reached level 99?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will you ever get another character to level 99 in the future?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did you get the runes for Infinity?",
    "answer": "I ran Lower Kurast 3000 times."
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy did you use to gain exp?",
    "answer": "I started by making a classic character and beating Hell in order to avoid completing my Ancients Quests. Then I converted my character to an expansion character and ran Chaos Sanctuary many times. At level 98 I completed Ancients Quests in Normal, Nightmare, and Hell."
  },
  {
    "question": "How did you keep track of all the drops?",
    "answer": "Each time a unique item, set item, or rune dropped, I manually entered it into a spreadsheet."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you share the spreadsheet raw data?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can download the raw data here in csv format.",
    "linkText": "drops.csv",
    "linkUrl": "src/data/drops.csv",
    "download": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have any other sites?",
    "answer": "Yes, a long time ago I made this Diablo 2 search site.",
    "linkText": "https://www.ocf.berkeley.edu/~gkwan/d2/search.html",
    "linkUrl": "https://www.ocf.berkeley.edu/~gkwan/d2/search.html"
  }
]